we have held 24 solution raisings
we have tackled every topic under the
sun
well no we fucked up we've tackled 24
but they fall under the category of
every topic under the sun
there is not a topic that we can't
vastly improve by getting people
together
for one hour and having a solution
rising
they fall under generally three
categories those that
get us what we need food clothing
shelter
education energy water
how could we create something that gets
an improvement in those areas in our
lives with ten thousand people and a
hundred thousand dollars
and every time we come up with a
powerful solution the other two things
that we've tackled is information
things that give us access to
information we can trust and use
because when you create it for 10 000
people it's created for the rest what
about
information on politicians that you
trust on science
on current events and the third
option are the big things that we feel
like we're too small to tackle
what could we possibly do when it comes
to war
or prisons or suicide
and every time every topic we have come
up with at least
one powerful adjacent possible to move
that area powerfully forward and if we
can come up with a solution to any area
we cannot put the solution to all the
areas
so what i want is for the world to host
solution raisins
people fall into one of three categories
so i invite you to do one of these three
things
if you are an influencer if you're
somebody who has fans has people who
care about what you say
and do hold a solution raising on a
topic that you care about
pick one topic
get some family and friends together
post it record it put it out for your
fans
invite them to do the same
one person doing that can
start bark a powerful powerful movement
two if you're like me and you don't
happen to have
much influence but you have a handful of
family and friends
start a solution raising club once a
week
pick a time that works for you call in
your friends that just want to complain
about everything and they haven't moved
on to the next two steps of
actually talking about the world they
want to create and then a powerful step
forward
it's actually possible right now with
ten thousand of us a hundred thousand
dollars
get together week after week and talk
about topics that you care about
tackle the three the things that you
need in your life that you would like an
improvement on
the areas of information that you can
see the overwhelm in society and you
want to have access to
information that you can trust and use
and the giant topics that feel too big
to tackle
what is what is something we could do
together
and the third option if you don't want
to talk to your friends and family and
get together weekly and and
and do the work that that entails come
to our solution raising
it's held every wednesday at 9 a.m
pacific standard time on zoom
join the facebook group to get access to
it and come create solutions to that
week's topic
share this with your friends and family
come create solutions that work
in a world that feels like it's falling
apart and people are waking up to how
our governments and corporations aren't
they don't have
solutions they don't have the meta
solutions we need to come together
and figure out how we move powerfully
forward and keep moving forward
in our own capacity and everyone can
participate everyone has a voice
all it takes is an hour of your time
every week
or if you're a celebrity good influencer
one hour one time with your friends
and put it out to your fans a better
world is on its way and we are all gonna
participate
in co-creating it together thank you